<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><w:document xmlns:mc="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/markup-compatibility/2006" xmlns:o="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" xmlns:r="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/relationships" xmlns:m="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/math" xmlns:v="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:vml" xmlns:wp="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/wordprocessingDrawing" xmlns:w10="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:word" xmlns:w="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/wordprocessingml/2006/main" xmlns:wne="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2006/wordml" xmlns:sl="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/schemaLibrary/2006/main" xmlns:a="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/main" xmlns:pic="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/picture" xmlns:c="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/chart" xmlns:lc="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/lockedCanvas" xmlns:dgm="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/diagram" xmlns:wps="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingShape" xmlns:wpg="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingGroup"><w:body><w:p w:rsidR="00000000" w:rsidDel="00000000" w:rsidP="00000000" w:rsidRDefault="00000000" w:rsidRPr="00000000"><w:pPr><w:contextualSpacing w:val="0"/><w:rPr><w:color w:val="a64d79"/></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r w:rsidDel="00000000" w:rsidR="00000000" w:rsidRPr="00000000"><w:rPr><w:rtl w:val="0"/></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve">Appointed in January 2015 as the Deputy Executive Director and Chief of Staff at the Port of Los Angeles, Doane Liu is the second in command at the busiest container port in North America and head of the Port’s External Affairs Bureau.     </w:t><w:br w:type="textWrapping"/><w:t xml:space="preserve">In this role, Liu is responsible for the Commission Office that works directly with the Los Angeles Harbor Commission; the Government Affairs Division that oversees legislative affairs at the federal, state, county, and city levels; and the Communications Group that includes the Community Relations, Graphic Services, Media Relations, and Trade Development divisions. Liu provides strategic external affairs leadership and support to Port senior management and the Harbor Commission regarding legislative policy, communications, and regional economic opportunities that require Port and City of Los Angeles collaboration.</w:t><w:br w:type="textWrapping"/><w:t xml:space="preserve">Liu joined the Port after serving as Deputy Mayor for the City of Los Angeles. He managed the Mayor's Office of City Services and helped the Mayor oversee 15 City Departments, including the Los Angeles Department Water and Power, Public Works, Transportation, Recreation and Parks, Public Library, and LA Zoo. He also established the Great Streets Studio and LA RiverWorks in the Mayor’s Office. A first-generation Korean-American, Liu also was a liaison in the Mayor’s Office to the Korean-American community in Los Angeles.</w:t><w:br w:type="textWrapping"/><w:t xml:space="preserve">Liu was previously Chief of Staff for Councilman Joe Buscaino and served as Chief of Staff for Councilwoman Janice Hahn, Deputy Mayor for Mayor James K. Hahn and District Director for Congresswoman Jane Harman. He was also Senior Vice President of Government Banking at JP Morgan Chase and Vice President in the Real Estate Industries Group at Security Pacific National Bank.</w:t><w:br w:type="textWrapping"/><w:t xml:space="preserve">Liu currently serves on the boards of the Los Angeles County Business Federation (BizFed) and Sister Cities of Los Angeles. He has previously served on the boards of Harbor Interfaith Shelter, Palos Verdes Peninsula Land Conservancy, Los Angeles Neighborhood Initiative, Los Angeles Regional Food Bank, Mary Star of the Sea High School, and Holy Trinity School. </w:t><w:br w:type="textWrapping"/><w:t xml:space="preserve">Liu graduated from the Wharton School at University of Pennsylvania and received an MBA from University of Southern California. He and his wife have four grown children and have lived in San Pedro for nearly 30 years.</w:t><w:br w:type="textWrapping"/><w:br w:type="textWrapping"/></w:r><w:r w:rsidDel="00000000" w:rsidR="00000000" w:rsidRPr="00000000"><w:rPr><w:b w:val="1"/><w:color w:val="a64d79"/><w:rtl w:val="0"/></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve">Program book ver.</w:t></w:r><w:r w:rsidDel="00000000" w:rsidR="00000000" w:rsidRPr="00000000"><w:rPr><w:rtl w:val="0"/></w:rPr></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="00000000" w:rsidDel="00000000" w:rsidP="00000000" w:rsidRDefault="00000000" w:rsidRPr="00000000"><w:pPr><w:contextualSpacing w:val="0"/><w:rPr><w:color w:val="a64d79"/></w:rPr></w:pPr><w:r w:rsidDel="00000000" w:rsidR="00000000" w:rsidRPr="00000000"><w:rPr><w:color w:val="a64d79"/><w:rtl w:val="0"/></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve">Appointed in January 2015 as the Deputy Executive Director and Chief of Staff at the Port of Los Angeles, Doane Liu is the second in command at the busiest container port in North America and head of the Port’s External Affairs Bureau.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:sectPr><w:pgSz w:h="15840" w:w="12240"/><w:pgMar w:bottom="1440" w:top="1440" w:left="1440" w:right="1440" w:header="0"/><w:pgNumType w:start="1"/></w:sectPr></w:body></w:document>