<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<w:document xmlns:wpc="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingCanvas" xmlns:mc="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/markup-compatibility/2006" xmlns:o="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" xmlns:r="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/relationships" xmlns:m="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/math" xmlns:v="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:vml" xmlns:wp14="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingDrawing" xmlns:wp="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/wordprocessingDrawing" xmlns:w10="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:word" xmlns:w="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/wordprocessingml/2006/main" xmlns:w14="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordml" xmlns:wpg="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingGroup" xmlns:wpi="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingInk" xmlns:wne="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2006/wordml" xmlns:wps="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingShape" mc:Ignorable="w14 wp14"><w:body><w:p w:rsidR="00AD5961" w:rsidRDefault="00AD5961" w:rsidP="00AD5961"><w:r><w:t>​Stephen Cheung is the President of World Trade Center – Los Angeles (WTCLA).  The WTCLA works to support the development of international trade and business opportunities for Southern California companies as the leading international trade association, trade service organization and trade resource in the Los Angeles region.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="00AD5961" w:rsidRDefault="00AD5961" w:rsidP="00AD5961"><w:r><w:t xml:space="preserve">Prior to his current role, Cheung was the Secretary General for Los Angeles Mayor Eric </w:t></w:r><w:proofErr w:type="spellStart"/><w:r><w:t>Garcetti</w:t></w:r><w:proofErr w:type="spellEnd"/><w:r><w:t xml:space="preserve">, and was responsible for managing policies and programs related to the Port of Los Angeles, Los Angeles World Airports, International Affairs and Global Trade.  Cheung served on the Board of Director of the Los Angeles Regional Export Council and the Los Angeles Business Council, and was the lead organizer for Mayor </w:t></w:r><w:proofErr w:type="spellStart"/><w:r><w:t>Garcetti’s</w:t></w:r><w:proofErr w:type="spellEnd"/><w:r><w:t xml:space="preserve"> international trade missions to Mexico, China, Korea and Japan.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="00AD5961" w:rsidRDefault="00AD5961" w:rsidP="00AD5961"><w:r><w:t>Concurrently, Cheung was the Director of International Trade for the Port of Los Angeles – the busiest container port in North America, and was responsible for developing programs to increase trade through the Port of Los Angeles, and facilitate goods movement through the Southern California region.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="00AD5961" w:rsidRDefault="00AD5961" w:rsidP="00AD5961"><w:r><w:t xml:space="preserve">Cheung joined the Port of Los Angeles and Mayor </w:t></w:r><w:proofErr w:type="spellStart"/><w:r><w:t>Garcetti’s</w:t></w:r><w:proofErr w:type="spellEnd"/><w:r><w:t xml:space="preserve"> Office after serving as Managing Director of International Trade and Clean Technology the City of Los Angeles.  He was responsible for enhancing international trade opportunities for Los Angeles-based companies, and expanding the city’s role as a leader in international trade, entertainment, tourism, manufacturing and professional services.  Cheung was the City’s lead organizer for the historic visit to Los Angeles by Chinese President, Xi Jinping in 2012.  Furthermore, Cheung implemented the city’s strategic plan to make Los Angeles a global capital of clean technology by building the infrastructure to support research, development and manufacturing with key partners such as the Los Angeles </w:t></w:r><w:proofErr w:type="spellStart"/><w:r><w:t>Cleantech</w:t></w:r><w:proofErr w:type="spellEnd"/><w:r><w:t xml:space="preserve"> Incubator and Port Tech LA.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="003D5E13" w:rsidRDefault="00AD5961" w:rsidP="00AD5961"><w:r><w:t xml:space="preserve">A proud </w:t></w:r><w:proofErr w:type="spellStart"/><w:r><w:t>Angeleno</w:t></w:r><w:proofErr w:type="spellEnd"/><w:r><w:t xml:space="preserve">, Cheung was born in Hong Kong and grew up in Los Angeles where he received both his bachelor’s in Psychobiology and master’s in Social Welfare from UCLA.  He currently teaches a graduate-level course on public policy at the Luskin School of Public Affairs, and serves on the Advisory Council of USC’s Center for International Business Education and Research and the Los Angeles </w:t></w:r><w:proofErr w:type="spellStart"/><w:r><w:t>Cleantech</w:t></w:r><w:proofErr w:type="spellEnd"/><w:r><w:t xml:space="preserve"> Incubator.</w:t></w:r><w:bookmarkStart w:id="0" w:name="_GoBack"/><w:bookmarkEnd w:id="0"/></w:p><w:sectPr w:rsidR="003D5E13"><w:pgSz w:w="12240" w:h="15840"/><w:pgMar w:top="1440" w:right="1440" w:bottom="1440" w:left="1440" w:header="720" w:footer="720" w:gutter="0"/><w:cols w:space="720"/><w:docGrid w:linePitch="360"/></w:sectPr></w:body></w:document>