<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><w:document xmlns:mc="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/markup-compatibility/2006" xmlns:o="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" xmlns:r="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/relationships" xmlns:m="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/math" xmlns:v="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:vml" xmlns:wp="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/wordprocessingDrawing" xmlns:w10="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:word" xmlns:w="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/wordprocessingml/2006/main" xmlns:wne="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2006/wordml" xmlns:sl="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/schemaLibrary/2006/main" xmlns:a="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/main" xmlns:pic="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/picture" xmlns:c="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/chart" xmlns:lc="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/lockedCanvas" xmlns:dgm="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/diagram" xmlns:wps="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingShape" xmlns:wpg="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingGroup"><w:body><w:p w:rsidR="00000000" w:rsidDel="00000000" w:rsidP="00000000" w:rsidRDefault="00000000" w:rsidRPr="00000000"><w:pPr><w:contextualSpacing w:val="0"/><w:rPr/></w:pPr><w:r w:rsidDel="00000000" w:rsidR="00000000" w:rsidRPr="00000000"><w:rPr><w:rtl w:val="0"/></w:rPr><w:t xml:space="preserve">Ms. Christie Hsiao is the Founder and Chief Executive Officer of Pacific Rim Entertainment Group, Inc. Ms. Hsiao serves as Creative Director for all of Pacific Rim’s projects, as well as overseeing all aspects of the marketing strategy, business development, continuance and growth. She was a Financial Analyst and managed the marketing departments for Yasuno. She is also an established Author with her debut title Journey to Rainbow Island due to hit the shelves November 14, 2013 accompanied with digital media, a video game and Journey to Rainbow Island feature film production. Ms. Hsiao is one of the key investors in Yasuno Trading &amp; New Vision International Co. She has strong government and entertainment industry ties throughout Asia and elsewhere in the world. Ms. Hsiao produced several independent films, including The Gold Retrievers with Billy Zane, Steve Guttenberg and Curtis Armstrong, Dark Honeymoon with Roy Scheider, Eric Roberts, Tia Carrere and Daryl Hannah and Love is the Drug with Lizzy Caplan, John Patrick Amedori, and Daryl Hannah. She consulted for several independent film and TV production companies since 2008. Ms. Hsiao launched her own production company dedicated to bridging American and international markets by developing projects with global appeal. Ms. Hsiao completed her first of seven novels, Joureny to Rainbow Island. She has been on a press tour for 6 months to create awareness about her new Joureny. Ms. Hsiao has been published in several magazines regarding Joureny to Rainbow Island including Variety magazine with a cover and full article. Ms. Hsiao studied film at NYU, where she wrote, directed and produced several well-reviewed short films. She has Bachelors Degree at UCLA, where Ms. Hsiao majored in Communications and East Asian Studies and has an MBA from Pepperdine University.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:sectPr><w:pgSz w:h="15840" w:w="12240"/><w:pgMar w:bottom="1440" w:top="1440" w:left="1440" w:right="1440" w:header="0"/><w:pgNumType w:start="1"/></w:sectPr></w:body></w:document>