<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<w:document xmlns:wpc="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingCanvas" xmlns:mc="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/markup-compatibility/2006" xmlns:o="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" xmlns:r="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/relationships" xmlns:m="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/math" xmlns:v="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:vml" xmlns:wp14="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingDrawing" xmlns:wp="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/wordprocessingDrawing" xmlns:w10="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:word" xmlns:w="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/wordprocessingml/2006/main" xmlns:w14="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordml" xmlns:wpg="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingGroup" xmlns:wpi="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingInk" xmlns:wne="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2006/wordml" xmlns:wps="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingShape" mc:Ignorable="w14 wp14"><w:body><w:p w:rsidR="003D5E13" w:rsidRDefault="00D31A80"><w:proofErr w:type="spellStart"/><w:r w:rsidRPr="00D31A80"><w:t>Nonny</w:t></w:r><w:proofErr w:type="spellEnd"/><w:r w:rsidRPr="00D31A80"><w:t xml:space="preserve"> de la Peña is pushing technological boundaries for narrative endeavors, including creating virtual reality environments for news, documentary and entertainment. To date, she has built multiple virtual reality constructs including a Formula 1 Singapore Grand Prix experience, Use of Force, which premiered at the Tribeca Film Festival, Project Syria, a commission by the World Economic Forum and Hunger in Los Angeles, which premiered at the Sundance Film Festival in January 2012. Her other projects include the MacArthur funded Gone Gitmo, a virtual Guantanamo Bay Prison; Cap &amp; Trade, an interactive exploration of the carbon markets; and Three Generations, a </w:t></w:r><w:proofErr w:type="spellStart"/><w:r w:rsidRPr="00D31A80"><w:t>newsgame</w:t></w:r><w:proofErr w:type="spellEnd"/><w:r w:rsidRPr="00D31A80"><w:t xml:space="preserve"> on the California eugenics movement. A fellow at the University of Southern California’s Cinema School, she spent two years as a Senior Research Fellow in Immersive Journalism at USC’s Annenberg School of Journalism and Communications. A graduate of Harvard University, she is also an award-winning documentary filmmaker with twenty years of journalism experience including as a correspondent for Newsweek Magazine and as a writer whose work has appeared in the New York Times, Los Angeles Times Magazine, Premiere Magazine, and others. Her films have screened on national television and at theatres in more than fifty cities around the globe, garnering praise from critics like A.O. Scott who called her work “a brave and necessary act of truth-telling.” While at USC, de la Peña is developing sophisticated linear narratives in virtual reality that explore the experiential nature of nonfiction and the feelings of presence that come with the connection to a digital representation of oneself. De la Peña’s other credits include as co-founder of </w:t></w:r><w:proofErr w:type="spellStart"/><w:r w:rsidRPr="00D31A80"><w:t>Stroome</w:t></w:r><w:proofErr w:type="spellEnd"/><w:r w:rsidRPr="00D31A80"><w:t>, a collaborative video sharing site which won a Knight News Challenge Grant.</w:t></w:r><w:bookmarkStart w:id="0" w:name="_GoBack"/><w:bookmarkEnd w:id="0"/></w:p><w:sectPr w:rsidR="003D5E13"><w:pgSz w:w="12240" w:h="15840"/><w:pgMar w:top="1440" w:right="1440" w:bottom="1440" w:left="1440" w:header="720" w:footer="720" w:gutter="0"/><w:cols w:space="720"/><w:docGrid w:linePitch="360"/></w:sectPr></w:body></w:document>