<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<w:document xmlns:wpc="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingCanvas" xmlns:mc="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/markup-compatibility/2006" xmlns:o="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" xmlns:r="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/relationships" xmlns:m="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/math" xmlns:v="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:vml" xmlns:wp14="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingDrawing" xmlns:wp="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/wordprocessingDrawing" xmlns:w10="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:word" xmlns:w="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/wordprocessingml/2006/main" xmlns:w14="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordml" xmlns:wpg="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingGroup" xmlns:wpi="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingInk" xmlns:wne="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2006/wordml" xmlns:wps="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingShape" mc:Ignorable="w14 wp14"><w:body><w:p w:rsidR="000E176E" w:rsidRDefault="000E176E" w:rsidP="000E176E"><w:r><w:t>In 2000, Frank Yang founded simplehuman with a goal to revitalize the trash can business. Today, not only is the Los Angeles-based design company the leader in stainless-steel step cans, but it also has expanded its vision—to design “tools for efficient living”—to more than 200 patented innovations and other products such as sensor soap pumps, kitchen and bathroom organization, and beauty tools, namely sensor mirrors.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="000E176E" w:rsidRDefault="000E176E" w:rsidP="000E176E"><w:r><w:t>​</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="000E176E" w:rsidRDefault="000E176E" w:rsidP="000E176E"><w:r><w:t>All simplehuman products embody efficient living design, a principle Yang, simplehuman founder, CEO and lead designer, defines as designing each product so it performs its intended task perfectly. To that end, all products are ergonomic,</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="000E176E" w:rsidRDefault="000E176E" w:rsidP="000E176E"><w:r><w:t>easy-to-clean, highly functional, and durable as well. Under Yang’s design direction, BusinessWeek/Industrial Design Society of America</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="000E176E" w:rsidRDefault="000E176E" w:rsidP="000E176E"><w:r><w:t>named simplehuman as one of the top corporations for Industrial Design Excellence in 2004. Yang has also garnered international design awards from organizations including reddot, the International Housewares Association and I.D. Magazine, and simplehuman's trash cans are considered among the most high-end cans on the market today due to their patented sensor technology and durability.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="000E176E" w:rsidRDefault="000E176E" w:rsidP="000E176E"><w:r><w:t>simplehuman products are available at fine specialty retailers in including Bed Bath &amp; Beyond, Williams-Sonoma, The Container Store, and Crate &amp; Barrel as well as the company’s website simplehuman.com.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="000E176E" w:rsidRDefault="000E176E" w:rsidP="000E176E"/><w:p w:rsidR="003D5E13" w:rsidRPr="000E176E" w:rsidRDefault="000E176E" w:rsidP="000E176E"><w:r><w:t>Yang has a B.A. in political science from UCLA. During his senior year, he decided to take an industrial design class, which is where he developed a passion for invention the idea of making existing products better. Yang was born in Taipei, Taiwan, and moved to Los Angeles when he was 11 years old. He grew up in the Palos Verdes area, where he still lives with his wife Sandy and two children.</w:t></w:r><w:bookmarkStart w:id="0" w:name="_GoBack"/><w:bookmarkEnd w:id="0"/></w:p><w:sectPr w:rsidR="003D5E13" w:rsidRPr="000E176E"><w:pgSz w:w="12240" w:h="15840"/><w:pgMar w:top="1440" w:right="1440" w:bottom="1440" w:left="1440" w:header="720" w:footer="720" w:gutter="0"/><w:cols w:space="720"/><w:docGrid w:linePitch="360"/></w:sectPr></w:body></w:document>