<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<w:document xmlns:wpc="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingCanvas" xmlns:mc="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/markup-compatibility/2006" xmlns:o="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:office" xmlns:r="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/relationships" xmlns:m="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/math" xmlns:v="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:vml" xmlns:wp14="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingDrawing" xmlns:wp="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/drawingml/2006/wordprocessingDrawing" xmlns:w10="urn:schemas-microsoft-com:office:word" xmlns:w="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/wordprocessingml/2006/main" xmlns:w14="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordml" xmlns:wpg="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingGroup" xmlns:wpi="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingInk" xmlns:wne="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2006/wordml" xmlns:wps="http://schemas.microsoft.com/office/word/2010/wordprocessingShape" mc:Ignorable="w14 wp14"><w:body><w:p w:rsidR="006D1A22" w:rsidRDefault="006D1A22" w:rsidP="006D1A22"><w:bookmarkStart w:id="0" w:name="_GoBack"/><w:bookmarkEnd w:id="0"/><w:r><w:t>Jackson Yang is the founder and CEO of Seville Classics, a globe-leading innovator and manufacturer in housewares and storage industry for more than 35 years. Under Mr. Yang’s visionary leadership, Seville Classics is dedicated in developing and crafting high quality products with latest designs, materials, technology, and sustainability.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="006D1A22" w:rsidRDefault="006D1A22" w:rsidP="006D1A22"/><w:p w:rsidR="006D1A22" w:rsidRDefault="006D1A22" w:rsidP="006D1A22"><w:r><w:t xml:space="preserve">Mr. Yang is also the Chairman of First General Bank, a bank mainly focus in providing services to small to medium sized business and individuals residing in Southern California. In 2012, First General Bank ranked 1st among nation’s best performing community banks by SNL Financial.  </w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="006D1A22" w:rsidRDefault="006D1A22" w:rsidP="006D1A22"/><w:p w:rsidR="006D1A22" w:rsidRDefault="006D1A22" w:rsidP="006D1A22"><w:r><w:t>Born in Changhua, Taiwan, Mr. Yang has common traditional Taiwanese characteristics with modest, pragmatic and diligent personalities.  He learned about International Business at the age of 16.  After immigrated to the United States in his early 40’s</w:t></w:r><w:proofErr w:type="gramStart"/><w:r><w:t>,  Mr</w:t></w:r><w:proofErr w:type="gramEnd"/><w:r><w:t>. Yang started his business from scratch. Today, he is now the CEO of this solid company making annual revenue well over US$200 million.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="006D1A22" w:rsidRDefault="006D1A22" w:rsidP="006D1A22"><w:r><w:t>Mr. Yang believes that entrepreneurs can only be considered successful when they start giving back to the societies.  During 2013-2014, Mr. Yang served as the President of World Taiwanese Chambers of Commerce to serve entire Taiwanese business persons worldwide.  In his tenure, Mr. Yang has flown around the world to communicate with many Taiwanese businessmen in different aspects to understand their needs, and also trying to combine all their power to help Taiwanese communities.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:p w:rsidR="006D1A22" w:rsidRDefault="006D1A22" w:rsidP="006D1A22"/><w:p w:rsidR="003D5E13" w:rsidRDefault="006D1A22"><w:r><w:t>Nowadays, Mr. Yang is actively involved in the Southern California communities by sharing his experience and wisdom.  Mr. Yang has two dreams in his life.  On one hand, for the seniors, Mr. Yang would like to build up a convenient community that comes with complete and professional health care system so that the seniors can live there worry-free and enjoy their retirement.  On the other hand, for younger generations, Mr. Yang is eager to share his successful experiences and resources to help them reach the excellence in their career lives.   Mr. Yang always encourages young entrepreneurs and working professionals to first learn how to deal with people, then how to set up the right attitude and put in effort, and lastly how to apply strategies to business.  By following such philosophy from Confucius 2000 years ago, Mr. Yang has set up an inspiring example for the Chinese American community.</w:t></w:r></w:p><w:sectPr w:rsidR="003D5E13"><w:pgSz w:w="12240" w:h="15840"/><w:pgMar w:top="1440" w:right="1440" w:bottom="1440" w:left="1440" w:header="720" w:footer="720" w:gutter="0"/><w:cols w:space="720"/><w:docGrid w:linePitch="360"/></w:sectPr></w:body></w:document>